{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "What is the original name of the 'El Robo' chapel?",
		            "content" : [
		                "San Francisco",
		                "Jerusalen",
		                "El Robo",
		                "Jesus del Gran Poder"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "When was the provisional chruch  of the Clarisas nuns stolen?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Wednesday, March 12th, 1790",
		                "Monday, January 10th, 1900",
		                "Wednesday, November 17th, 1649",
		                "Wednesday, January 20th, 1649"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "How is the chapel considered, nowadays?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Cultural Heritage of Humanity",
		                "The Rute of the 7 Churches",
		                "Heritage of Ecuador",
		                "The Monument of Quito"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
				}
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "What name is Garcia Moreno street called?",
		            "content" : [
		                "7 cruses street",
		                "La Ronda street",
		                "Yavirac street",
		                "Guaragua street"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "How many churches does the Garcia Moreno street have?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Three",
		                "Six",
		                "Seven",
		                "Nine"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "When was Carmen Bajo church built?",
		            "content" : [
		                "16th century",
		                "20th century",
		                "18th century",
		                "15th century"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
				}
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "Why was the Catedral Church destroyed?",
		            "content" : [
		                "The Catedral Church was destroyed because of an eartquake",
		                "The Catedral Church was destroyed to rebuild with stones bases",
		                "The Catedral Church was destroyed by the Spanish people",
		                "The Catedral Church was destroyed by people"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Is the Catedral Church located in Quito center?",
		            "content" : [
		                "No, it is not",
		                "I do not know",
		                "Yes, it is",
		                "It does not say"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What design does the Catedral Church have in the ceiling?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Catedral has designs of 'Pan de Oro' in the ceiling",
		                "Catedral has designs of 'Marmol' in the ceiling",
		                "Catedral has designs of 'Wood' in the ceiling",
		                "Catedral has designs of 'Metal' in the ceiling"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 0
				}
		    ]
		},
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "What styles does San Francisco church have?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Baroque",
		                "Mudejar",
		                "Beautiful",
		                "A and B are correct"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What did Cantu√±a hide?",
		            "content" : [
		                "A piece of paper",
		                "One pound of sugar",
		                "A stone",
		                "The Hell"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "When did the first reconstruction of San Francisco church start?",
		            "content" : [
		                "in 1642",
		                "in 1645",
		                "in 1651",
		                "in 1699"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
				}
		    ]
		}
	]
}